Honestly, I always like listening to a song that sometimes makes me cry because it has a really beautiful message.
We are the world. We are the children.
We are the world. We are the children. We are the hope.
And I think we should come together more and more each day as a community, as a race, as people,
no matter the color, the height, the age, it doesn't matter where you're from or where you come from,
what matters is that you can contribute something beautiful to this gorgeous planet, so that not only we enjoy it, but also those who come after us.
It can be.
Much love.
Lots, lots, lots
of beautiful energy.
And a lot of
personal work for everyone.
So that we can be happy.
And thank you very much.
Thank you, man.
Thank you to you, my friend.
Thank you.